Hello developers!
開発者の皆さん、こんにちは。
Today, I'll introduce "Miyabi" - a framework that automates everything
今日は、Issue作成からPR完成まで 完全自動化する「Miyabi」をご紹介します。
from Issue creation to PR completion.
Miyabiは21個の専門AIAgentが協力して、
Miyabi has 21 specialized AI Agents working together
あなたが寝ている間にコードを書き、
to write code, run tests, and create Pull Requests while you sleep.
テストを実行し、 Pull Requestまで作成します。
It's simple to use. Just two commands to start Miyabi.
使い方は簡単です。 たった2つのコマンドでMiyabiが起動します。
First, set your GitHub token as an environment variable.
まず、GitHubトークンを 環境変数に設定。
Then, run "miyabi work-on" with an issue number.
次に、miyabi work-on コマンドで Issue番号を指定するだけ。
The Coordinator automatically breaks down tasks
これで、Coordinatorが自動的にタスクを分解し、
and assigns them to specialist agents.
専門Agentに割り振ります。
Let's see it in action.
では、実際の動作を見てみましょう。
Issue #270 is "Enable TypeScript strict mode".
Issue #270は 「TypeScript strict modeを有効化せよ」です。
First, Coordinator analyzes the issue.
まず、しきるん（Coordinator）が Issueを分析。
Next, CodeGen generates the code.
次に、つくるん（CodeGen）が コードを生成。
Reviewer checks the quality.
めだまん（Reviewer）が品質チェック。
Finally, PR Agent creates a Pull Request.
最後に、まとめるん（PR Agent）が Pull Requestを作成。
You don't need to do anything.
この間、あなたは何もする必要がありません。
All agents work together automatically.
全てのAgentが自動で連携して動きます。
Miyabi has 21 specialized agents.
Miyabiには21個の専門Agentがいます。
7 Coding Agents: Coordinator, CodeGen, Reviewer, PR Maker,
開発系7個： しきるん、つくるん、めだまん、まとめるん、
Issue Analyzer, Deployer, Hook Manager.
イシュまる、デプろう、フックマン。
14 Business Agents: Entrepreneur, Marketer, Sales, CRM,
ビジネス系14個： 起業ちゃん、マーケ太郎、セールス姫、
Analytics, Content Creator, SNS Strategist, YouTuber, and more.
CRMくん、データ子、コンテンツ君、 SNS太郎、YouTube姉さん、など。
They all work together to support your development.
全員が協力して、 あなたの開発を支援します。
Miyabi is fully open source.
Miyabiは完全オープンソースです。
Star it on GitHub now and try it in your projects.
今すぐGitHubでStarして、 あなたのプロジェクトでも試してみてください。
Detailed documentation, Quick Start guide,
詳細なドキュメント、 クイックスタートガイド、
and all 21 agent specifications are available.
そして21個のAgent仕様が 全て公開されています。
Let's enter a new era of development with AI.
さあ、AIと一緒に開発する新しい時代へ。
Make development more fun and faster with Miyabi. Thank you for watching!
Miyabiで、開発をもっと楽しく、もっと速く。 ご視聴ありがとうございました！